tlo.com 2016-04-01

# TLO Privacy Statement

Privacy  
We are committed to protecting your privacy  
Please carefully read our privacy policy to understand how we will treat the information you provide while visiting our Website. 

The collection and use of information   
When you visit our Website, we collect the following information about you and your visit. 

**Information that you provide us** – We collect information that you provide to us by completing applications or other forms on our Website. In general, we will use the information you provide for the purpose for which it was provided, such as to provide you with information about our services. As a general rule, we will not share this information with unaffiliated third parties unless you permit us to do so. 

**Internet information** – We may also collect general Internet data about your Website visits, including which of our web pages you visited and how long you spend on each page. This is to better understand how our Website is used and what areas are of interest to our visitors. To collect this information, when you visit our Website, a "cookie" or a “Flash® cookie” may be set on your computer. Cookies and Flash cookies contain information that allows our web servers to recognize you whenever you visit. We do not provide this information to outside parties other than for purposes of improving and enhancing your experience on our Website. No personal information is stored in cookies. Your web browser should allow you to manage cookies and you can manage your Flash cookies by [clicking here](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html). “Flash” is a registered trademark of Adobe Systems Incorporated. 

In addition, we may use Google Analytics to obtain anonymous information collected from other websites on which we display advertisements that are designed to bring visitors to our Website. We use this information to understand how visitors, who arrive at our Website by clicking on those advertisements, interact with our Website. We may also use this anonymous information to enhance or modify our advertisements. You may opt-out of this anonymous data collection and sharing activity through the Google Analytics Privacy Overview web page at www.google.com and following the procedures noted under the Browser Opt-out section. 

Disclosures required  
Circumstances may arise requiring us to disclose personally information to third parties. These include as may be required by law or pursuant to judicial or governmental investigations or proceedings, or in connection with contractual obligations or corporate transactions such as a merger. 

Security  
We have appropriate security measures in place to safeguard the personal information we maintain about you. 

Changes to this Privacy Policy  
We may modify this policy at any time by posting the modified terms on this page. Please check the policy each time you use our Website for the most current information. 

### Market-leading risk management solutions

  * Verify identity
  * Prevent and detect internal and external fraud
  * Link people, businesses, and assets
  * Conduct enhanced due diligence
  * Increase the effectiveness of current fraud prevention and legislative compliance programs
  * Identify relationships between customers, people, and businesses
  * Investigate potential conflicts of interest

* * *

* * *

## Get to know TLOxp

* * *
